## **Justin**

## **Angeles**

28278 N. Clagstone Rd Athol, ID 83801 (208) 886-0743 JUSTINAAWD@GMAIL.COM

### Skills

7 years in customer service / sales positions. Have never missed a day of work and always aim to be the hardest worker in the room. I work well with people from all walks of life. Experience leading teams of 5-7 while managing a gym and leading teams of 10-20 at a call center.

# **Experience**

February 2020 - September 2020

**Inspiro**, Coeur D'Alene - Account Executive for Dish Network

- Top 10% in sales across the nation right out of training.
- Developed scripts to help boost the teams numbers.
- Inbound sales including running credit checks.

December 2018 - February 2020

**Qualfon, Coeur D'Alene** - Sales Lead / Trainer

- Over twice the sales of second place in our biggest annual sales competition.
- Helped grow the department from 50 150 agents.

August 2014 - February 2018

The Fitness Place, Alaska - Gym Manager / Fitness Coach

- Was promoted within 2 months of being hired, work any hours needed.
- In charge of hiring and training new team members.
- Counted the till nightly and made deposits to the bank.

### Education

August 2010 - May 2014

Kenai Central High School, Alaska - Graduate

#### References

Scott Jackson - Fitness Place Owner - 907-398-4157

Chris Glidden - Qualfon Supervisor - 208-676-7801

Mike Phillips - Inspiro Coach - 877-467-7476